Guide to the National Association of Manufactures Pamphlets 1945-1969
National Association of Manufactures Pamphlets
- NAM Publications, 1951; Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Item 14: Research and Development Board, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
    By Edwin A. Speakman. 12/7/1951. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: The Course of Human Events, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
    By William H. Ruffin. 12/7/1951. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Economic Consequences of a National Wage Policy Based on Automatic Escalation and Productivity Adjustments, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
    By Dr. Leo Wolman. 12/6/1951. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: The Nature of the Beast, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
    By Robert Vogeler. 12/5/1951. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Personally Speaking, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
    By Miss Ginger Rogers. 12/6/1951. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Industry's Views on Health, Welfare, and Pension Plans Under Stabilization, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
    By Clifford F. Hawker. 12/6/1951. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: A Free Press in a Free World, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
    By Dr. Edwin D. Canham. 12/6/1951. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: Opening Remarks, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
    By J. Warren Kinsman. 12/6/1951. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: The Consequences of Capitalism, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
    By Winthrop H. Smith. 12/6/1951. Item is in English.
  - Item 23: Mobilizing Your Sales Forces for Freedom, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
    By Robert A. Whitney. 12/6/1951. Item is in English.
  - Item 24: Christianity in Industry, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
    By George W. Strake. 12/6/1951. Item is in English.
  - Item 25: What's Ahead for Wage Stabilization?, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
    By Nathan P. Feisinger. 12/6/1951. Item is in English.
  - Item 26: Inflation Stopped or Slumbering, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
    By Emerson P. Schmidt. 12/5/1951. Item is in English.
  - Item 27: 22nd NAM Institute on Industrial Relations, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. October 15-19, 1951. Item is in English.
  - Item 28: Selected NAM Publications Dealing with Industrial Relations, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Item 29: Preserving the Management Function in Collective Bargaining, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Item 30: Leadership and the Management Equation, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
    By Stanley C. Hope. March 9, 1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 31: News from the NAM, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. May 7, 1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 32: News from the NAM, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. Press Release June 18, 1958. Item is in English.
  - Item 33: Government for the People, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
    By Ernest G. Swigert. 12/4/1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 34: Symposium on The Will of the People Today and Tomorrow, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. 12/4/1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 35: Remarks of Senator Charles E. Potter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
    By Senator Charles E. Potter. 12/4/1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 36: An Address by Hon. Graham A. Barden, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
    By Graham A. Barden. 12/4/1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 37: Remarks by Hon Clarence J. Brown, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
    By Hon. Clarence J. Brown. 12/4/1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 38: Remarks of Senator John L. McClellan, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
    By Senator John L. McClellan. 12/4/1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 39: Remarks by Dr. Joseph Kaplan, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
    By Dr. Joseph Kaplan. 12/4/1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 40: Man Looks at a Small Planet, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
    By Dr. R.W. Porter. 12/4/1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 41: Can Labor Clean its House?, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
    By Sylvester Petro. 12/4/1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 42: The Right to Work, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
    By Rev. John E. Coogan. 12/4/1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 43: Is the Public Protected by Present Labor Laws?, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
    By Hon. Carl T. Curtis. 12/4/1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 44: Symposium on Individual Rights or Organized Wrongs, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
    By Mr. Virgil Day. 12/4/1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 45: Remarks by George Bronner, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
    By George Bronner. 12/4/1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 46: Remarks of Jack Boory, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
    By Jack Boory. 12/4/1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 47: Remarks of N. Floyd McGowin, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
    By N. Floyd McGowin. 12/4/1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 48: Remarks of W.B. Prosser, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
    By W.B. Prosser. 12/4/1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 49: A Report on American Business, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
    By William Bynum. 12/5/1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 50: Does Business Size Make Any Difference on the Really Big Issues?, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
    By R. Harland Shaw. 12/5/1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 51: Symposium on The Businessman's Opportunities in Public Affairs, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. 12/5/1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 52: Challenges Facing All Business, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
    By David M. Molthrop. 12/5/1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 53: Tax Reform to Strengthen America, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
    By WM J. Grede. 12/5/1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 54: Is Foreign Aid Spending a Benefit or a Burden?, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
    By Senator John J. Sparkman. 12/5/1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 55: Women's Role in the Community Picture, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
    By Milton C. Lightner. 12/5/1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 56: Debate on Is Foreign Aid Spending a Benefit or a Burden?, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Item 57: A Sound Economy Means Economy in Government, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
    By Senator Harry F. Byrd. 12/5/1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 58: The Washington Scene, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
    By Stephen f. Dunn. 12/5/1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 59: The Growing Shadow of Labor in Public Affairs, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
    By Cola G. Parker. 12/5/1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 60: Public Affairs is a Do-It-Yourself Job, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
    By Charles R. Sligh, Jr. 12/5/1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 61: The Bill of Rights - Our Heritage, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
    By Judge Harold R. Medina. 12/6/1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 62: Education, Strategy, and Fourth Dimensional Warfare, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
    By Frank Rockwell Barnett. 12/6/1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 63: Public Power vs. Private Power, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
    By Dr. S.C. Hollister. 12/6/1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 64: A Special Employee Relations Division Report, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. 11/9/1955. Item is in English.
- NAM Publications, 1955-1959; Publication (Box 2, Folder 14)
- NAM Publications, 1947-1954; Publication (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: A Guide to Human Relations Within the Enterprise, Publication (Box 2, Folder 15)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. May 23-25, 1954. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Three Ways to Build Confidence in America's Future, Publication (Box 2, Folder 15)
    By Don Belding. 12/1/1954. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: America's Human Potential, Publication (Box 2, Folder 15)
    By Earl Bunting. 12/1/1954. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: New Economic Horizons for the Atomic Age, Publication (Box 2, Folder 15)
    By John Jay Hopkins. 12/1/1954. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Taxes and America's Future, Publication (Box 2, Folder 15)
    By Fred Maytag II. 12/1/1954. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: An Address By Meyer Kestnbaum, Publication (Box 2, Folder 15)
    By Meyer Kestnbaum. 12/1/1954. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: The New Look in Europe, Publication (Box 2, Folder 15)
    By C.H. Kaars Sypesteijn. 12/2/1954. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: America's Future in World Affairs, Publication (Box 2, Folder 15)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. 12/2/1954. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: The Struggle in Asia, Publication (Box 2, Folder 15)
    By Carlos P. Romulo. 12/2/1954. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: The Corporate Citizen, Publication (Box 2, Folder 15)
    By Reuben B. Robertson, Jr. 12/2/1954. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Which Way America, Publication (Box 2, Folder 15)
    By Ralph J. Cordiner. 12/2/1954. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Our Spiritual Assets, Publication (Box 2, Folder 15)
    By O. Frederick Nolde. 12/2/1954. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Our Foreign Economic Policy, Publication (Box 2, Folder 15)
    By Clarence B. Randall. 12/3/1954. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: You and the Classroom Teacher, Publication (Box 2, Folder 15)
    By Dr. Arthur G. coons. 12/3/1954. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Atomic Energy and What it Means, Publication (Box 2, Folder 15)
    By Dr. John Ray Dunning. 12/3/1954. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Creating Markets- The Key to Progress, Publication (Box 2, Folder 15)
    By William L. McGrath. 6/8/1954. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: NAM Employee Relations Division, Publication (Box 2, Folder 15)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. 6/11/1946. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: NAM Employee Relations Division, Publication (Box 2, Folder 15)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. 9/3/1946. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: NAM Employee Relations Distribution, Publication (Box 2, Folder 15)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. 7/7/1950. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: Management Answers to Some Union Objections on Wage Incentives, Publication (Box 2, Folder 15)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. 11/22/1949. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: NAM Employee Relations Division, Publication (Box 2, Folder 15)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. 11/15/1949. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: Employee Handbooks, Publication (Box 2, Folder 15)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. July 1953. Item is in English.
  - Item 23: The Closed Shop, Publication (Box 2, Folder 15)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. 6/1/1949. Item is in English.
  - Item 24: The Closed Shop, Publication (Box 2, Folder 15)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 25: Effective Employer-Employee Communications, Publication (Box 2, Folder 15)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. January 1948. Item is in English.
  - Item 26: Preparing to Negotiate, Publication (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Item 27: NAM's Views on Equal Pay for Equal Work, Publication (Box 2, Folder 15)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. 1/30/1953. Item is in English.
  - Item 28: Factors to Consider in Establishing a Profit-Sharing Plan, Publication (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Item 29: Selected References on Profit Sharing, Publication (Box 2, Folder 15)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. 8-17-1950. Item is in English.
  - Item 30: Brief Notes on Industry's Experience with Profit Sharing, Publication (Box 2, Folder 15)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. July 25, 1950. Item is in English.
  - Item 31: Selected References on Wage Incentives, Publication (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Item 32: Pension Plans, Publication (Box 2, Folder 15)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. 6/24/1948. Item is in English.
  - Item 33: Fundamentals of Job Analysis and Evaluation, Publication (Box 2, Folder 15)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. 11/24/1949. Item is in English.
  - Item 34: Selected References on Job Analysis and Evaluation, Publication (Box 2, Folder 15)
- NAM Publications, 1952-1961; Publication (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: New Horizons in Management, Publication (Box 2, Folder 16)
    By H.C. Clellan. April 6, 1954. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Teaching Aids, Publication (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Item 3: Calling All Jobs, Publication (Box 2, Folder 16)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. November 1954. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Calling All Jobs, Publication (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Item 5: Industry Believes, Publication (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Item 6: Your Opportunities in Management, Publication (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Item 7: The Issue of the Shorter Work Week, Publication (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Item 8: What's Wrong with Labor Arbitration?, Publication (Box 2, Folder 16)
    By F.A. O'Connell. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Instructor's Manual for Productivity, Publication (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Item 10: Productivity Gauge of Economic Performance, Publication (Box 2, Folder 16)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. September 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Employment Stabilization, Publication (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Item 12: The Challenge of Right Living in Labor-Management Relations, Publication (Box 2, Folder 16)
    By Claude A. Putnam. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Unemployment Compensation in a Free Economy, Publication (Box 2, Folder 16)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. July 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Instructor's Manual for Productivity, Publication (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Item 15: Unemployment Compensation in a Free Economy, Publication (Box 2, Folder 16)
- NAM Publications, 1952; Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Health Service in Industry, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Handbook of NAM Activities and Services for Education Industry Cooperation, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. October 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Industrial Relations Policy Statement, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. December 2, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Employment Stabilization, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: The Federal Lobbying Act- Comments on NAM v. McGrath, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
    By Raymond S. Smethurst. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: How the Steel Dispute May Affect You!, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: Who Lost the Steel Strike?, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: Compulsory Unionism, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Item 9: Military Preparedness and the American Economy, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
    By Leslie C. Arends. December 3, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: What Happens When You Speak Up?, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
    By H.E. Humphreys, Jr. December 3, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Trade and Trends - Some International Problems, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
    By John Suman. 12/4/1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: The Problems We Face, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
    By Senator Wallace F. Bennett. 12/3/1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Leadership versus Oblivion, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
    By Earl Bunting. 12/3/1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Foreign Assistance and the American Economy, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
    By H.W. Prentis, Jr. 12/3/1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Teamwork Through Better Understanding, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
    By Howard M. Dirks. 12/3/1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Effect of Government Policies on Labor, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
    By Dr. Leo Wolman. 12/4/1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Our Foreign Policy, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
    By Stanton Griffis. 12/3/1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: The Employer's Role in Employee Benefits, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
    By Harold C. McClellan. 12/3/1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Champion of the American Competitive Enterprise System Since 1895, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Item 20: The Effect of Government Policies on Industry Government and Industry Exchange Views, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
    By Colonel Willard Chevalier. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: Bringing Government Back Home, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
    By Judge Francis Cherry. 12/4/1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: Washington and You, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
    By Walter Chamblin. 12/4/1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 23: Bring Government Back Home, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
    By Harley L. Lutz. 12/4/1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 24: Women and Government, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
    By Miss Marion E. Martin. 12/4/1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 25: The Other Side of the Tracks, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
    By WM White. 12/4/1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 26: Atomic Energy in Industry- Tomorrow, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
    By Dr. W.L. Davidson. 12/5/1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 27: Industry and Future Problems in Atomic Energy, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
    By L.R. Hafstad. 12/5/1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 28: National Association of Manufacturers Remarks, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
    By Charles H. Weaver. 12/5/1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 29: Common Sense for the Common Good, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
    By WM J. Grede. 12/5/1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 30: An Address by Gen. Douglas MacArthur, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
    By Gen. Douglas MacArthur. 12/5/1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 31: An Address by Gen. Douglas MacArthur, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Item 32: Talking it Over with Employees, Stockholders, and Dealers, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Item 33: Develoments on the Labor-Management Front, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Item 34: Earning Opportunities for Mature Workers Facts, Obstacles, and Points of View, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
    By John M. Convery. 7/8/1953. Item is in English.
  - Item 35: Some Management Views on Manpower in the Event of a Partial or Total War Emergency, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. December 1953. Item is in English.
  - Item 36: What's Ahead for Taft-Hartley, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. 12/4/1953. Item is in English.
  - Item 37: Talking it Over with Employees Stockholders & Dealers, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Item 38: Present Status of Labor-Management Relations Act, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
    By George W. Armstrong, Jr. 4/22/1953. Item is in English.
  - Item 39: 24th NAM Institute on Industrial Relations, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. March 16-20, 1953. Item is in English.
  - Item 40: Loopholes in the Labor Laws, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. May 1958. Item is in English.
  - Item 41: The Guaranteed Annual Wage and its Implications to a Free Economy, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. February 1954. Item is in English.
- NAM Publications, 1953-1958; Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
- NAM Misc. Leaflets, 1945-1966; Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Employee Communications Folders, Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: The Real Aims of Union Leadership, Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. April 1958. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The Economic Background for Social Action, Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Contract and Contract Negotiation Problems under the Labor-Management Relations Act, Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. 8/22/1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Labor Under Federal Law, Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. 10/30/1946. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Hiring Handicapped People, Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. November 1955. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: NAM Leadership in the Field of Employee Relations, Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. April 1954. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: The Real Issue in Steel, Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. 8/18/1949. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Leadership for Industrial Harmony, Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. March 16, 1953. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Cross Currents in the Labor Scene, Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
    By G.E. Morse. 12/3/1954. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Changeor consequences: Our Industrial Relations Future, Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
    By Richard J. Anton. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Medicine in an Industrial Society, Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
    By Maxwell C. Weaver. 1/25/1955. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Company Group Insurance Programs, Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. 8/19/1953. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: NAM Industrial Relations Department, Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Item 15: Present Status of Labor-Management Relations Act, Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. 4/22/1953. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Some Notes Relating to the Guaranteed Annual Wage and its Implications, Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Item 17: NAM Employee Relations Division, Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Item 18: Employment of the Physically Handicapped and Older Workers, Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. September 1949. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Seven Keys to Unemployment, Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
    By Professor David McCord Wright. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: Is Automation Causing Unemployment?, Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
    By Ralph W. Ells. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: Unemployment in an Expanding Economy- The Long View, Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Item 22: The Coming Crisis in Labor Law, Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
    By Dr. Carroll E. French. Item is in English.
  - Item 23: Preparing to Negotiate, Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
- NAM Publications, 1959; Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Should a Man Have to Join a Union to Work?, Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Employee Communications for Better Understanding, Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. November 1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: What do Labor and Industry have the Right to Expect from Each Other?, Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Some Dos and Don'ts for Supervisors, Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: TVA-Full Steam Ahead?, Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. June 1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Principal Provisions of 20 White Collar Union Agreements, Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. March 1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Radiation Hazards-Workmen's Compensation, Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Item 8: Freedom to Choose, Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Item 9: Labor-Management Relations A Look Ahead, Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
    By Charles R. Sligh, Jr. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Let's Have Action to Clean up the Labor Movement, Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Item 11: Let's Have Action to clean up the Labor Movement, Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Item 12: The Real aims of Union Leadership, Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Item 13: Unatom A Plan for the Development of a United Atomic Treaty Organization of Free World Nations, Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
    By John Jay Hopkins. 11/29/1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Toward the Five-Year Goal, Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)